To be continued next time
It'll be fun to shake ourselves.
Why don't we just go with it?
Sure, why not?
Let's just keep going, shall we?
Ready?
Hello! Here's your shirt!
Yay!
So, I'd like to start off by asking, are you confident in your underwear?
Yes!
Oh! Time to prove that statement!
Wow, I'm so happy! I've been wanting to prove it!
Yes, that's why this project is
We're going to expand the Cachouletics with shirts!
Yay!
Yes! You know that thing Hama-chan does on TV?
You eat something ordinary, plus something a little more extravagant, and then decide which one is the more extravagant.
I know what you mean!
I'd like to see if everyone can guess!
I've been alive for 25 years!
You are very confident, Hon-chan!
Where did you get that confidence?
What? From here!
From here!
Pal looks strong!
A cook seems to know a lot of things!
I don't know.
He seems to know what he's doing!
When someone comes over for the first time and asks what's in this?
You say!
This is ginger! This is miso! This is miso!
I guess that's part of it...
I have it! I'm sure of it!
I can see that!
How about you? What about Yuzuki?
I think Yuzuki is a person who eats a lot of common things!
If you eat something unusual, it's different from what you usually eat!
I think I'm going to be like that!
I see!
Before we start rating, I'd like to give a penalty game to the person who didn't answer the question the best.
Let's decide what the penalty game will be!
But you know, you can do this not once, but with many different ingredients!
So, I'm just going to say...
So, what do you call it... giving a sad title?
Give a sad title?
A title?
Yes, a title.
I see what you mean.
Tasteless Representative.
Oh, no!
Mr. Tastebuds!
That's the worst!
Tastebuds.
Oh no!
That's a name.
So you're going to be a taste addict.
There's always a group like that when you come to this corner.
Oh...
Taste Ontarians.
It's been on this YouTube for a while now.
If we could all answer all the questions correctly.
That's right.
That's why we're here.
That's what we're trying to achieve.
So you're not a tastemaker.
That's right.
Then, if everyone gets it right...
To Mr. Samgay Shachi.
Oh, my God.
They did this to me already?
Congratulations!
First of all, we have grape juice!
We're going to drink one grape juice each, divided into A and B.
One is the common 100 yen, 100 yen per night
And the other is a quite luxurious grape juice for 900 yen!
I'll compare the 100 yen grape juice and the normal ishii grape juice.
You can guess which one it is by your reactions.
Okay, Ami, I'll start drinking first, whichever comes first.
You mean the same thing will be handed over?
Yes.
We'll close our eyes and see if we can tell by the color.
Then we all swallow.
Okay, then.
If I finish this, can I open my eyes?
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay.
Let's drink the first juice.
Cheers.
Wait a minute.
Are you making fun of us?
Uh, wait a minute.
This is the bumper.
Hey, did you even try it out?
Are you kidding me?
It's ours.
Okay, then B, please.
Okay, let's all have a B, please.
Yum! It's so good!
I love them both!
Thank you!Thank you!
I'll take it!
I can already tell!
I know!
Then tell me which one was the luxury juice.
Answer me with an idly!
Ready!
A!
Correct!
Yay!
The texture is different.
It's like the moment you get to Ethibir.
It's not the usual, right?
This was a sommelier.
Maybe it was the sommelier.
Sommelier?
And the cooter was totally different.
It was a different kind of rich, thick, luxurious.
It was a beaver.
That's what I always drink.
It's delicious.
Next, we'll compare the 100 yen cheese and the Normal Ishii cheese.
You can guess which one it is by your reactions.
That's about half a bag of cheese.
Around here?
Huh!
Yikes!
Yay!
Yes!
The goal is to separate us.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's kind of important to get the camera.
Okay, let's do it.
Do you want me to put my hand out?
Yes, ma'am.
How do you want me to do it?
I'm gonna scoop it into my hand.
Spoon.
Ready?
I got it. I got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm-hm.
Can I open my eyes for this?
Yeah, you can eat it.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
It's delicious.
It's kind of creamy and kind of filmy.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry about that.
I still have my eyes closed.
Oh, shit.
Can I open them after I eat?
It tastes amazing.
Did everyone get theirs?
Let's have some of that beautiful cheese.
Is this really the wrong kind of cheese?
Not even close.
Wrong kind of cheese.
You can open your eyes.
Not even close.
Oh, my God. So, did you guys have a decision?
Curious, which is A and which is B?
Ready!
B!
Correct!
That was easy.
Is it a different kind of cheese?
Because the cheese smells different.
It's the wrong kind.
Cheezers, blues...
There was a lot of cheese in there.
It's like polo.
It says "natural cheese.
They're both natural.
Natural cheese is still natural cheese.
But it's not the same.
It's different. It's different.
It seems so easy. So far.
It's kind of easy until you get to the halfway point.
Then it gets harder and harder.
I can't do it at all.
It's okay.
Let's do it.
Wait, maybe we're...
We're screwed.
Really?
That's definitely not true.
[ED]